raycasting2D is a demo and implementation of a raycasting algorithm coded in following along with The Code Train. 
The walls are randomly generated and will be different on each refresh. the particle in the which radiates the 
rays will follow 'perlin noise' around the screen.

You can also click the mouse to swap between auto-walk mode and follow mode. Follow mode will cause the particle 
to follow the mouse around the screen. Returning to auto-walk will cause the particle to return to it's original path.
